Approach Archives
Approach Archives
- APPROACH files
  - Issues files
    - #42, Winter, 1962 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, note on John Berry's THE FLIGHT OF WHITE CROWS, title page, contributors, insert, H. Fowler's report to editors, some page proofs, publicity letter from Dodd, Mead about Marie Chay's PILGRIM'S PRIDE, printing receipts, copyright assignments for Jane Esty's "An Unworthy Season," Robert L. Tyler's "Deposition of Don Quixote," Chad Walsh's "Population Explosion," James T. Brunot's "The Skin Dive" letter from John Edward Hardy, editor with John Logan of short story textbook requesting same for Ray Smith for "When Springwinds Boom," "A Summer's Loss," "Seaboard Burial Ground," "At the Art Institute," "On This Green Hill," "Because My Starstruck Nights," "The Coming of Venus," "The Greening Tree," "Winter Wind," his "Eve" and "Eden Diary" published under International Copyright and letter from Smith covering same, clipping from N.Y. Times 11/12/61 of review of Berry's book, flyer for Winifred Rawlins' RUSSIAN PICTURES, 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #43, Spring, 1962 (Box 1)
      15th anniversary issue letters to end from JHM, letters from Sam Bradley about a) French translation of Berdayev "On Suicide" and letters to Morosov, director of YMCA Press of Paris who published same carbons of insert, cover, contributors' notes, Index, title page, original card of Thomas Merton's "If You Seek a Heavenly Light," request and granting of permission for use of H. Fowler's "Interpreting the APPROACH Story," which appeared in TRACE No. 17 and copy of same, page proofs, from S.B. b) letters from Limbach Co. granting permission to use Jacob Landau's woodcut & copies of same, vita of Joseph Luke Agneta, c) about ad in TRACE, from ESQUIRE refusing our ad, letters to and from Simon Doniger of PASTORAL PSYCHOLOGY about an ad in that magazine, copy of letter to selected libraries covering gift of SCYLLA THE BEAUTIFUL and acknowledgments from Albright College Library, Amherst, Atlanta University, Ruth Stephan Poetry Center, Ball State Teachers College, Boston Public Library, Bowdoin, The British Museum, Bryn Mawr, Bucknell, University of California at Los Angeles & Berkeley, Chicago, Colorado, Cornell, Delaware, Dickinson College, Duquesne, Earlham, Guilford, Harvard, Haverford, Tulane, Indiana, Kansas State University, Kentucky, Lebanon Valley College, Lincoln University, Los Angeles Public Library, Louisiana State, Michigan State, Minnesota, Moorehead State College, Nebraska, N.Y. Public, State University of N.Y. at Morrisville, Northwestern, Pennsylvania, Princeton, Purdue, Rutgers, Smith College, Southern Methodist, Stanford, Temple, Texas, Union, Washington and Lee, Williams College, Yale, printing receipts, names for publicity letters, permissions granted to William Stafford for "Conservative," W. R. Moses for "Emblem: Beaver," and "One Time on One River," Lewis Turco for "Mrs. O'Malley," "For Aunt Cossie, Who Must Die" and "Scarecrow," 2nd class mailing receipt, contributors' addresses
    - #44, Summer, 1962 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons on Note on Nist's MODERN BRAZILIAN POETRY, contributors' notes, cover proof, carbon for insert, vita from Elaine Greenspan, letters to-and from publicity director at Indiana University Press about reviews for the above mentioned Nist book and Carolyn Kizer's THE UNGRATEFUL GARDEN, H. Fowler's notes for make-up, printing receipts, 2nd class mailing receipts, permissions request from Borestone Mountain Poetry Awards for Exta Williams Wolking's "Metamorphosis," permissions granted for same and William Stafford's "On Quitting A Little College," Mother Mary Anthony's "Election," "Many Mansions," "Husbandry," and "Rockabye," contributors' addresses
    - #45, Fall, 1962 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, H. Fowler's report to editors, originals of bits on Faulkner and John Holmes, carbons of title page, insert, contributors, proof of cover, from S. Bradley on Philip Silver's translation of Mora's book on Unamuno, letters, copy and proof of THE FAT ABBOT ad in APPROACH, card from Mary Fowler, printing receipts and 2nd class mailing receipts, permission request from Jerome Mazzaro's "Port-au-Prince," contributors' addresses
    - #46, Winter, 1963 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, title page, insert, contributors' notes, obits of e e cummings and Hermann Hesse and clipped obits of same from N.Y. Times, clipping of picture of 3rd century fish from Thuburbo Majus, cards from Philip Silver & Alan Swallow, H. Fowler's working make-up, letters to and from SIENANDOAH about exchange of ads, permission asked for and granted of BELOIT POETRY JOURNAL for John Nist's translation of Carlos Drummond de Andrade's "Childhood," and Indiana University Press for Nist's translation of Jorge de Lima's "Rag Doll," copyright permission to Hugh Zachary for "Where There Is Gold," request for permission to translate Nist's Brazilian Modernism" in REVISTA DE CULTURA BRASILENA, letter from Harper & Row about Stafford's TRAVELING THROUGH THE DARK and refusing to take an ad in APPROACH, printing receipts, 2nd class mailing receipts, cards returned from insert, contributors' addresses
    - #47, Spring, 1963 (Box 1)
      H. Fowler's report to the editors, letters to and from JHM, carbons for insert, William Carlos Williams obit, contributors, Index, cover proof for first art work on cover, correspondence with Naomi Christensen about Reed Whittemore essay, letters asking permission and permission grants from University of Minnesota Press for lines from AN AMERICAN TAKES A WALK and with MacMillan to quote from Whittemore's THE SELF MADE MAN and THE BOY FROM IOWA and copy of contract, cancelled check showing payment and letters requesting duplication of payment and copy of check, part of letter from Robert B1y, letters from Herman Elstein, make-up of insert advertising APPROACH to be put in Pendle Hill's pamphlet written by Mrs. Thorne on Quaker poets, letters to and from THE ACTIVIST about their use of Ayala's article without acknowledging either the translators or prior publication in APPROACH, letter from M.G. Jacobs, printing receipts, 2nd class mailing receipts, permissions granted to John B. Hughes and Miguel Gonzalez Gerth, translators and Francisco Ayala author of "The Writer in the Mass Society," contributors' addresses; note on distribution
    - #48, Summer, 1963 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, H. Fowler's tentative make-up, carbons of cover, contributors' notes, APPROACHing, original and 2nd versions on note of Dorothy Gilbert Thorne's POETRY AMONG FRIENDS (a Pendle Hill pamphlet), proofs of art work, first draft of Ralph Luce's "Sea Town," letters from Insel-Verlag about permissions and payment for Salinger's translations of 2 Rilke poems, letter from Pendle Hill publications about the APPROACH flyer in the above pamphlet, permissions to Daniel Hoffman for "Climbing Katandin," Gerald Locklin for "Hart Crane," request from Borestone Mountain for Ann Stanford's "The Protestant, and David Clark's "Metaphora Mundi," also permissions granted to Norma McLain Stoop for "Landscape Without Figures," and to Mark McCloskey for "Prothalamion," note on distribution, printing and 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #49, Fall, 1963 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, first draft of Albert Fowler's "Holy Violence," 2 cards from Sam Bradley, carbons of tentative make-up, cover, insert, title page, contributors' notes, note on Daniel Hoffman's THE CITY OF SATISFACTIONS, letter from copyright office on non-receipt of their copies, letters to and from James Hanes with rough draft and proof of his cover, permissions granted Jocelyn Macy Sloan, for "Figure of a Priest," Thomas Whitbread for "Old Coat," David R. Clark for "Metaphora Mundi," printing & 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #50, Winter, 1964 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, 1st & 2nd versions of title page, insert, C.S. Lewis obit, contributors, letter from David Bragdon and card from Henry Bragdon, part of a letter from Anne G. Sneller, letter from Benjamin Britten's secretary, clippings from the NATION, 11/16/63 and NY TIMES Magazine, 11/17/63 on Britten, letter from Post Office correcting our wording about 2nd class postage, requests for permissions from Borestone Mt. for: Ronald B. Ribman's "Magellan: 1521," Harold Witt's "Into Mountains," Winifred Rawlins; "Vincent," Alberta T. Turner' "Things In Love," Helen Morgan Brooks' "A Young David," grant to Ribman, note on distribution, printing & mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #51, Spring, 1964 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of index, contributors' notes, cover, 2 versions of title page, announcement of the APPROACH Prize Poem for 1963: Mildred Cousens' "Questions Requiring No Answers," carbons of Helen Fowler's letters to Arthur Lawson & Biagio Pinto, card from Sam Bradley, card from Robert Sward, letter from Thomas Merton's secretary about A. Fowler's article "Possessed by the Holy Spirit: the poetry of Thomas Merton & Vassar Miller, publicity on Merton's EMBLEMS OF A SEASON OF FURY, clipping of ad from NY TIMES 1/24/64 announcing Stafford's winning the Shelley Memorial Award, permissions for inclusion of Witt's "Dogs have as much right as people in Nevada" in Scott, Foresman's school text anthology, printing & 2nd class mailing receipts, note on distribution contributors' addresses
    - #52, Summer, 1964 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JIM, carbons of tentative make-up, note on Elizabeth Randall-Mills' COUNTRY OF THE AFTERNOON, cover, 2 versions of title page, APPROACHing, contributors' notes, letter from Gonzalez Gerth, to and from the Makler Gallery, Virginio Ferrari, Aldo Casanova, permissions granted for Mildred Cousens' "Questions Requiring No Answer," Alberta Turner's "Things in Love," Philip Appleman's "Kites on a Windy Day" & "A Malediction, Forbidding Morning," Robert Wallace's "Lines for a Friend" & "Susan," Stanley Cooperman's "The Moulting" & "Mount Hebron," distribution note, printing & 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #53, Fall, 1964 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of title page, change in editors, cover, and contributors' notes, negative of Sklarow's photo of Esherick's "Reverence", catalogue of Bethell-Wilkinson's one-man show, letters to John Reilly Parrish and Joseph Tanda, permissions granted Eleanor A. McQuilkin for "A Mountain in my Pocket," to Helen Morgan Brooks for "A Young David," to Harold Witt for "Into Mountains," to Winifred Rawlins for "Vincent," to Theodore Holmes for "Uncle Henry, to Marvin Bell for "Believable Linden, etc." to Ida Fasel for "Metope" & "On the Bridge," note on distribution, printing & 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #54, Winter, 1965 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of tentative make-up, cover, note on Gertrude Scwebell's CONTEMPORARY GERMAN POETY: AN ANTHOLOGY, announcement of 1965 Bragdon Awards, title page, contributors' notes, purchase order, correspondence with David McReynolds about our plug of the 1966 Peace Calendar, requests from American Poets Fellowship for inclusion of "Union Station" by Charles Tinkham, "Chez James" by Arnold Lazarus, and "Two Sketches" by Lewis Turco in their anthology, permissions granted for same, printing and 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #55, Spring, 1965 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, title page, T.S. Eliot obit, announcement of 1965 API)ROACH Awards to Robert Wallace for "Susan" and to Philip Murray for "Marcus Aurelius," contributors' notes, index, page proofs of the Johns Hopkins & Wesleyan University Press ads in APPROACH, correspondence with Warren Kliewer about en APPROACH ad in RELIGIOUS THEATRE, carbon copy and their proof of ad, requests for 1965 THE POETS VIEW anthology for Felix Stefanile's "Nocturne," Audrey Fernandez' "The Saints," & Richard Curry Esler's "Watchman, What of the Night?" grants for the same, grants to Harold Witt for "Doves," to Joseph Joel Keith for "Man in the Back Room," to Laurence Lieberman for "No One to Blame," to Robert Wallace for "The House," to Albert Fowler for all his material in APPROACH to date, printing & 2nd class mail receipts, distribution note, copyright law, contributors' addresses
    - #56, Summer, 1965 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, Harold Vinel obit, title page, contributors' notes, A. Fowler's reworking of Jack Tootell's "Elijah," proofs of ads in NY Review of Books, letter to and from the manager of Vassar Cooperative Bookshop, printing & 2nd class mail receipts, contributors' addresses plus review notices for books reviewed in the issue
    - #57, Fall, 1965 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, title page, contributors' notes, carbons of letters to John Hultberg & Lee Brown Coye, letters to and from Carol Murphy, letters from Sam Bradley, page proof 1966 Award flyer, letters requesting & granting the Auden quotes from Random House, notation of source of quotes, permissions granted to Helen Fowler for all work in APPROACH to date, printing & 2nd class mailing receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #58, Winter, 1966 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, working lay-out, carbons of cover, 1966 award announcement, title page, contributors' notes, proof of cover & note for illustration, proof of ad for Sam Bradley's book, correspondence with Dennis Hale of THE ACTIVIST about APPROACH ad and working copy for same, letters commending issue from Sam Bradley, Alan Brilliant, the Rev. Robert Pollard III, Joseph Joel Keith, Carroll Arnett, Ann Fortenberry, permission granted Carroll Arnett for "The Promise," printing & 2nd class mail receipts, distribution note, contributors' addresses
    - #59, Spring, 1966 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, title page, contributors' notes, index, proof of 1966 Awards to Don Mager for "Choreograph" & Constance Carrier "At Tripolis," letters to and from THE ACTIVIST about exchange of ads, our proofs of their ad and copy of Larch 1966 Activist, letters from David McReynolds of WRL about our note on their Peace-Calendar and proofs of same, proofs of title page, letters about exchange of ads with THE WESTERN HUMANITIES REVIEW, copy of letter to David Bragdon, copy of private printing of °Footnote to a Crusade," catalogue of 160st annual exhibit at Pa Fine Arts Academy, showing prize to Reilly, letters to Mildred Monge & Robert McGovern, letters from Charles Ufford, Audrey Fernandez, Barbara Chapin, receipt for ad in NY REVIEW OF BOOKS, receipt for print of Reilly picture, receipt for listing in Franklin Square periodical handbook, letters & enclosures from Cecil D. Smith disapproving of avant-garde poetry, notices from Post Office about zip codes, permissions granted Audrey Fernandez for "Resurrection," to Harold Witt for "My Sudden Cousin;" distribution note, printing & 2nd class mailing. receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #60, Summer, 1966 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, letter to Theodore Holmes about use of his letters to Albert Fowler and makeup copy for submission to him, clipping from Knopf Quarterly News Notes about Frank O'Connor's death, carbons of APPROACH Poetry Awards, cover, title page and contributors' notes, letters about this issues being a Little Magazine of the Month in the club file, letters to & from George P. Elliott about reprinting the Mager poem, letters to and from Smith Alumnae Quarterly about reprinting the Carrier poem, letter from Betsy Colquitt about corrections, letters to and from Dr. Robinson about corrections, letter to H. M. Brooks about correction, letters from Elizabeth Green, Jocelyn Sloan, Barbara Christopher, Don Mager about the dedication to L.L. (which Laurence Lieberman, one of the judges, thought might be taken to refer to him) letters from Sam Bradley, permissions granted for: Stanwood K. Bolton, Jr.'s "A Perhaps for the Frogs," Don Meur's "Choreograph," Charles Philbrick's "Declensions oz Summer," Laurence Lieberman's "Hands and the Fisherman's Wife," Barbara Howes' "The Lovers of Delicate Things," Constance Carrier's "At Tripolis," printing & 2nd class mail receipts, distribution note, contributors' addresses
    - #61, Fall, 1966 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, carbons of cover, title Page, contributors' notes, proof of Exposition Press ad in APPROACH, requests from Borestone Mt for Carroll Arnett's "The Promise," Laurence Lieberman's "Hands & The Fisherman's Wife," Felix Stefanile's "Letter from a Friend in Exile, Hayden Carruth's "Concerning Necessity," & J.H. McCandless' "God Will Be A Little Late This Year," permissions granted McCandless, Carruth & Stefanile for the same, letters from Dennis Trudell, William Heyen, Hayden Carruth, David Madden, Wm. E. Byerly, letter about including Harold Witt's "Bees, Suns and Blueberry Muffins at the Dickinsons" in the projected Dickinson anthology, printing & 2nd class :ail receipts, distribution note, letters & memos from the Post Office re zip codes, contributors' addresses
    - #62, Winter, 1967 (Box 1)
      letter to JHM, carbons of "Approach Authors Appear," cover, title page, contributors' notes, of letter to John Reilly, new rejection slip, Exposition Press contract for ad, printing receipts & same for 2nd class mail, note on distribution, contributors' addresses plus review copy notices
    - #63, Spring, 1967 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JR:, carbons of cards sent to subscribers about the last issue, cover plus original tracing by Sam Bradley), Alan Swallow obit (clipping from NY TIMES Book Review 12/18/66) title page, contributors' notes, H. Fowler's notes on cutting Albert Fowler's "From Fish God to Fools Island," letter about 230 copies of this issue for class use, letters from Alan Brilliant, Teo Savory, Margaret Menamin, William Hull, letters from Roy Proctor, permissions granted Philip Appleman for "summer Love and Surf," for Dilys Laing's "Declaration of War on Me," "Poem:, note on distribution, printing & 2nd class mail receipts, contributors' addresses
    - #64, Summer, 1967 (Box 1)
      letters to and from JHM, 1st draft of "Credit Lines," rejected histories of APPROACH, returned letter to An Index to Book Reviews in the Humanities, letter from Henry Bragdon, distribution note, master file on subscriptions, copy of account with Bryn Mawr Post Office, printing & 2nd class mail receipts, Borestone Mountain Poetry Awards from Winter '67 "Mark Twain" by Paul Petrie (copyright grant in #62 plus Waddell Austin's letter) and Kenneth F. Rosen's "Cows" and Philip Appleman's "Summer Love and Surf" from Spring, 167. Permissions for both the latter in #63.
  - Correspondence, contributors and authors
    [This subseries includes] correspondence with APPROACH contributors plus letters from a few well-known authors. (N.B. Such files were not kept systematically before 1955, a few letters were kept in the first 8 issue files and are still there; the rest of the correspondence is lost); letters from APPROACH editors.
    - Agneta, Joseph Luke (Box 1)
    - Aiken, Conrad (Box 1)
    - Allen, John (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Wendell (Box 1)
    - Angell, Barbara (Box 1)
    - Ames, Bernice (Box 1)
    - Anselm, Felix (Box 1)
    - Antoninus, Brother (William Everson) (Box 1)
    - Appleman, Philip (Box 1)
    - Arnett, Carroll (Box 1)
    - Awner, Max (Box 1)
    - Baker, Donald W. (Box 1)
    - Balaban, John (Box 1)
    - Barrows, Richard L., Jr. (Box 1)
    - Bartlett, Elizabeth; Baybars, Taner; Beecher, John (Box 1)
    - Bell, Charles (Box 1)
    - Bell, Marvin (Box 1)
    - Berland, Jayne (Box 1)
    - Berlind, Bruce (Box 1)
    - Berry, John (Box 1)
    - Berthoff, Warner (Box 1)
    - Beum, Robert (Box 1)
    - Bice, Clare (Box 1)
    - Black, Charles (Box 1)
    - Bly, Robert, "a few letters lost" (Box 1)
    - Bradley, Sam (Box 1)
    - Bragdon, David (Box 1)
    - Bloom, Robert; Bock, Frederick (Box 1)
    - Bolton, Stanwood X., Jr. (Box 1)
    - Brentlinger, Patrick (Box 1)
    - Brian, Lee (Box 1)
    - Brooks, Helen Morgan (Box 1)
    - Brown, Harper (Box 2)
    - Brown, Rosellen (Box 2)
    - Browne, Michael Dennis (Box 2)
    - Brunot, James T. (Box 2)
    - Buckley, F.R., See Crumpet, Peter
    - Burch, Charles (Box 2)
    - Bukowski, Charles (Box 2)
    - Byron, Stuart (Box 2)
    - Carrier, Constance (Box 2)
    - Carruth, Hayden (Box 2)
    - Casanova, Aldo (Box 2)
    - Chapin, Barbara (Box 2)
    - Chay, Marie (Box 2)
    - Childs, Barney (Box 2)
    - Christensen, Naomi (Box 2)
    - Christopher, Barbara (Box 2)
    - Clark, David R. (Box 2)
    - Codey, Regina (Box 2)
    - Coffield, Glen (Box 2)
    - Cole, Lois Dwight (Box 2)
    - Colquitt, Betsy Feagan (Box 2)
    - Cooperman, Stanley (Box 2)
    - Conrad, R. William (Box 2)
    - Cousens, Mildred
    - Coye, Lee Brown; Crandall, Ruth (Box 2)
    - Crowley, J. V. (Box 2)
    - Crumpet, Peter (F. R. Buckley) (Box 2)
    - Cunningham, Julia (Box 2)
    - Cutler, Bruce (Box 2)
    - de Longchamps, Joanne (Box 2)
    - de Martelly, Janet (Box 2)
    - Docili, Alexandra and Peter (Box 2)
    - Domino, Ruth (Mrs. Mario Tassoni) (Box 2)
    - Donovan, Alan (pen name of Evelyn Thorne, q.v.) (Box 2)
    - Doughty, LeGarde S. (Box 2)
    - Drake, Jack (Box 2)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward (Box 2)
    - Eberman, Willis (Box 2)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 2)
    - Eibel, Deborah (Box 2)
    - Eller, Ruth (Box 2)
    - Elliott, William I. (Box 2)
    - Elstein, Herman (Box 2)
    - Emblen, D. L. (Box 2)
    - Empringham, Douglas R. (Box 2)
    - Enslin, Theodore (Box 2)
    - Esler, Richard Curry (Box 2)
    - Esty, Jane (Box 2)
    - Evans, Abbie Huston (Box 2)
    - Evans, J.A.S. (Box 2)
    - Everson, William, See Antoninus, Brother.
    - Fandel, John (Box 2)
    - Fasel, Ida (Box 2)
    - Farber, Norma (Box 2)
    - Fernandez, Audrey (Box 2)
    - Ferrini, Vincent (Box 2)
    - Fiedler, Leslie A. (Box 2)
    - Flanner, Hildegarde (Box 2)
    - Flowers, Nancy (Box 2)
    - Foster, Ruel E. (Box 2)
    - Fowler, Albert (Box 2)
    - Fowler, Mary D. (Box 2)
    - Fox, Ruth Berrien (Box 2)
    - Francis, Robert (Box 2)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd (Box 2)
    - Fraser, Kathleen (Box 2)
    - French, Warren (Box 2)
    - Friedman, Norman (Box 2)
    - Friedrich, Gerhard (Box 2)
    - Frumkin, Gene (Box 2)
    - Fuchs, Patricia D. (Box 2)
    - Frost, Robert, complete works, not listed (Box 2)
    - Gardner, Delbert R. (Box 2)
    - Garrett, George (Box 2)
    - Geiger, Don (Box 2)
    - Gersh, Gabriel (Box 2)
    - Gibbs, Margaret (Box 2)
    - Gibson, Walker (Box 2)
    - Gilmore, Edith (Box 2)
    - Gonzalez Gerth, Miguel (Box 2)
    - Gray, James (Box 2)
    - Gree, Scott (Box 2)
    - Greenberg, Arnold (Box 2)
    - Greene, Jonathan (Box 2)
    - Greenspan, Elaine (Box 2)
    - Greenwood, Robert (Box 2)
    - Grutzmacher, Harold (Box 2)
    - Guenther, Charles (Box 2)
    - Gunn, Louise (Box 2)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 2)
    - Hall, Walter E., Jr. (Box 2)
    - Hamburger, Michael (Box 2)
    - Hanes, James (Box 2)
    - Harten, Jaap (Box 2)
    - Hazo, Samuel (Box 2)
    - Hejinian, C. H. (Box 2)
    - Heyen, William. (Box 2)
    - Hiner, James (Box 2)
    - Hoffman, Daniel (Box 2)
    - Holmes, James S. (Box 2)
    - Holmes, John (Box 2)
    - Holmes, Theodore (Box 2)
    - Hovde, A. J. (Box 2)
    - Howes, Barbara (Box 2)
    - Hoy, John C. (Box 2)
    - Huddleston, Blanche (Box 2)
    - Hudson, David H (Box 2)
    - Hudson, Deatt (Box 2)
    - Hughes, John B. (Box 2)
    - Hull, William (Box 2)
    - Hultberg, John (Box 2)
    - Jerome, Judson (Box 2)
    - Johnson, Olive (Box 2)
    - Jones, Mary Hoxie (Box 2)
    - Judson, John (Box 2)
    - Kaplan, Ellen (Box 2)